http://www.wragbarn.com/privacy_policy

Course Status
Wrag Barn Golf Club: 10/12/2020 - COURSE, CLUBHOUSE AND PRO SHOP OPEN. driving range and short game area open for visitors, Buggies only if you have medical exemption & should be kept to paths & the rough and then adhering to the 90 degree rule >
Tel: 01793 861327
Login |
Book a Tee
HomeLoginGolfGolfCourse OverviewMembershipGreen FeesSocietiesPro ShopGolf AcademyGolf OpensPolicies WeddingsWeddingsCivil CeremoniesReceptionGroundsWedding PackagesGalleryTerms & Conditions ConferencesFunctionsFunctionsTribute NightsSunday LunchesPartiesWakes Contact us
Privacy Policy
Wrag Barn Management Limited are committed to protecting your privacy and rights. We strive to be transparent about how your personal information is used, and we are committed to using your personal information in accordance with all applicable data protection laws.
Our Privacy Notice Explains:
What information we collect from you?
Why we collect this information?
Who might we share this information with?
How will we secure your information?
How long do we keep hold of your information?
How can I access the information you hold about me?
Changes to this policy.
What information we collect from you?
We may collect your name, email address, postal address and phone number when making an enquiry, booking an appointment or requesting a brochure.
Why do we collect this information?
The information collected is used to respond to requests, arrange appointments, services and products that may be of interest to you and inform you of any subsequent changes to the information we provide.
Who might we share this information with?
We do not sell or share your information to any third parties.
How will we secure your information?
We ensure that there are appropriate technical controls in place to protect your personal data. For example, we ensure that any online forms are encrypted, and our network is protected and routinely monitored. Your personal data will only be accessible by appropriately trained staff whose job roles require such access.
How long do we keep hold of your information?
We will store your personal information only for as long as we consider it necessary to carry out the activities documented above. Regular reviews are carried out and where data is found to be no longer relevant, the data is securely deleted.
How can I access the information you hold about me?
If you have any queries regarding this Privacy Notice, how your data is used or would like to request information regarding what data of yours that we hold please contact our Data Protection Officer, Wrag Barn Management Limited, Shrivenham Road, Highworth, Swindon, Wiltshire, SN6 7QQ. Email
info@wragbarn.com.
Changes to this policy
Changes to this privacy policy will be posted to this page so that you are kept informed of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. This policy was last updated on 25th May 2018
Testimonials
This was the perfect venue for my Daughters wedding that took place on Saturday 1st Sept. Thank you to all the Staff that helped make this a really great day, the food was lovely and we couldn't have asked for a better day. Thank You!
Gail Cutbail
This is just a test for my Daughters wedding that took place on Saturday 1st Sept. Thank you to all the Staff that helped make this a really great day, the food was lovely and we couldn't have asked for a better day. Thank You!
Web Development
Shrivenham Road, Highworth, Swindon, Wiltshire SN6 7QQ
01793 861327
info@wragbarn.com
NewsletterYOUR EMAIL
©2020 Wrag Barn Golf Club. All Rights Reserved
|
Privacy Policy
Created by intelligentgolf version 10.1.2.
© 2020 Wrag Barn Golf Club. All Rights Reserved.
